The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives a magicless boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the next wizard king.
Though Asta's situation is practically unheard of,
there are others residing in this kingdom
who possess at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely use spells at all.
They make up a very small minority,
living their lives in the shadows.
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
The group of kidnappers led by Dasu Tayak and Bo Nocte,
who had originally identified themselves as the Devil Banishers,
were later revealed to be called the Devil Believers,
those who worship the Devil.
After their true intentions were made known,
the Devil Believers murdered Kavwe
and the other Magic Parliament members whom they had manipulated.
then left with Nero and Asta's grimoire.
So what, you think they might want to offer Nero as a gift?
Huh. It reminds me, they still have the kids' grimoire too.
Once they pay tribute, they'll defect to the Spade Kingdom,
or rather the Devil inside it.
Right. Good luck.
Asta and the other Black Bulls set out after the Devil Believers.
It's gonna be pretty difficult to catch them,
if they manage to make it past Breed Mountain in this weather.
Look down there, I think I see them!
Yeah?
They finally managed to catch up.
However...
How are there so many?
This is insane!
Yeah?
That's insane!
This is insane!
It does seem...
I think it's insane!
This is insane!
It's insane!
So, when I first go
Until my first lash line
I fall through this set
So, when I fall into this
I hear from you can't stop
I'm taking the束 of the dynamic
Always____ to something
Shine like a demon
No part of this season
Truth ou voou quoie-la te
Now do mo, na, dou mo
You also, the match with me
On the way we wave
We're aiming to go crazy
It's forever
You shine like a diamond
It's all like a diamond
How lovely
The sunset
Oh, yes, of course
I honestly hadn't noticed it
It only takes a few brief moments for the sun to go down
But it always shines so brilliantly until the very last second
It's such a peaceful thing to watch, don't you think?
Yes
Sorry, is your name Bo Nocte?
You live in the forest on the outskirts of town, right?
You've heard of me?
Yes, my mother-in-law's mentioned you before
Let me guess
She told you to avoid that strange woman who makes those questionable medicines
No, it's nothing like that
Is that what those are for?
Yes
Wow, you're incredible
How so?
Well, most people in this kingdom use magic for everything
But you actually make things yourself
Where did you learn how to create medicines like that?
Nowhere, really
What?
I learned all that I could about different herbs
Then I kept trying until something worked
All alone?
I barely have any magic ability
So I figured out the one thing I could do and stuck with it
I should be going
Oh, wait
My name is Dazu
Dazu Tayak
I hope this isn't too presumptuous
But could I visit you sometime?
Of course
It'd be nice to see you again
I'll even make a batch of medicine for you
If you'd like to learn
This is great
The bombs you make are so effective
Looks like we're clear to keep moving forward
We should hurry before it gets too dark
We need to pass through Breed Mountain and cross the border as quickly as we can
Once we do, we'll be out of the Clover Kingdom's jurisdiction
That way, even if the Magic Knights find us, they can't do anything
We'll be in Spade before long
No, you won't
Even if you get out of the Clover Kingdom without being cut
You'll still have to go through a strong magic region on the way
The Spade Kingdom is a mysterious land covered in snow and secrets
Between there and the Clover Kingdom lies a neutral zone belonging to no nation
Most of this area is classified as a strong magic region
The term strong magic region refers to a place that possesses a powerful force field of mana
Which causes various magical phenomena that keep outsiders at bay
This and other harsh conditions make these places quite treacherous
Getting through a strong magic region is a difficult task even for a magic knight
So how do you expect to do it with almost no magic ability to speak of?
Well, you bring up a good point
Do you plan to die?
Die?
I suppose that's a possibility
But it's enough to know that we have a chance
Let's go
Right
Hey, Captain Yami, this is Magna
Let me know if you can hear me
We tracked down the Devil Believers, but they got us pretty outnumbered here
So we're waiting for your orders, boss
Are you there?
Come in
Some mana in this area seems a little messy
And we're close to the border where that strong magic region is
So that might be why the signal's bad
All right, you two
I'm gonna look for a spot with better reception so I can talk to Captain Yami
Stay here so I know where to find you
I'll come back soon with reinforcements and then we'll be ready to roll
Let's kick it into hockey and crazy cyclone
Hey, Magna, wait up
We have to stay out here in this rain for too much longer
Then we're going to catch cold for sure
Though they say idiots can't catch cold
So Asta's safe
What's the matter with you the second he tells us to stay put you go barreling up the mountain?
I'm worried about Nero
Believe me, I want to rescue Nero too, but we need some kind of plan
Could we make them scatter somehow?
No, that won't work
Then what are you thinking?
I'll talk to them some more
Maybe we'll understand each other better
If it were that simple, then we wouldn't be in this mess right now
Nero
Good grief, you're so stubborn
Come on
I'll help you get up there
You'd better say thank you
Thank you so much, Noelle
Sure, it's fine
But, uh, you owe me one
Whoa, you okay?
Yeah
I'll be all right
Here, take my hand
Thanks
I can't stop shaking
It's even colder now that the sun's going down, isn't it?
Yes, but we have to press on
Thinking back on everything I've been through
This is nothing at all
After everything I've been through, this is nothing
You're exactly right
Beautiful
Just like back then
A full moon
Perhaps the mana will be weaker in the strong magic region
The odds may be against us
But there's still a chance
Thanks to chance, I was able to meet you
And to make it this far
You've helped me get through so many trials and hardships, Bo
I'm eternally grateful
So am I
We've come such a long way
But we still have a very difficult road ahead of us
Then let's keep working together
You and me
What's that?
Could it be?
Look
Asta
We've finally tracked you down
Nero, where are you?
Hey, wait
Something isn't right
I'm sure you're too dumb to notice it
But I'm not detecting much mana from these people at all
Just like that boy we saw back in the village
He only had that faint, fleeting mana
Is it really that common for people in our kingdom to have such weak magic power?
If this is just some of them, how many more are there?
Founder
Nero! We're here to save you!
Hey, be more careful
It's fine
The wind's real strong
So if they try to hit us with a sleep potion or something, it'll blow away
It's still pretty risky, though
We're magic knights
We're supposed to protect these people, not fight them
But Asta's my squadmate
I have to protect him, too
Now what?
Master Asta, they're really here
That's him, the one who's been blessed with the Devil's power
They're praising Asta
Because they worshiped the Devil
You're Dazutayak, the leader, right?
Asta
And you're Bo Nocte
You can't have Nero
She's really important to us and we have to bring her home
I know what you're doing
You think that if you give Nero and my grimoire to the Spade Kingdom, they'll say you can join forces with them
Good plan
Too bad you don't have me
If you know all that, then one thing should be clear
There's no way we can give your friend back
After you cross these mountains, you'll be on neutral ground
The strong magic region up ahead won't be as bad tonight since there's a full moon
So I'm guessing you're gonna try to push through
But with so many people, there's no way you'll all make it
We're well aware
Even so, I
We must press on
I barely have any mana
So I can only use small spells
As you know, magic is everything in the Clover Kingdom
So I was regarded as worthless
I might as well have never been born
Even my own parents looked down on me
I was bullied
My teachers mocked me and I couldn't make friends
Everyone gave me dirty looks
I'm sure you understand, Asta
Yeah
That's why I worked so much harder than my peers
But no matter what I did, my lack of magic ability always made me the target of disgust and ridicule
But you weren't alone
Your husband accepted you, right?
Accepted me?
When that old lady Maggie from Tuliu talked about you
She said your mother-in-law was happy that her son had married such a wonderful girl
I know things were hard
But at least you had a family who loved you the way you were
So even if you didn't have much power, you were still happy about that, weren't you?
I wasn't happy at all
I knew how they really felt
Maybe if they had lived
No, people are all the same
Every day I spent with them
Was a nightmare
They always smiled at me
Told me my cooking was delicious
And complimented my hard work
That's good!
I'm sure our neighbors saw my husband and his mother as kind, charitable people
But behind closed doors, they still mocked me
They looked down on me
Just like everyone else
Those two didn't accept me at all
They were only using me
They enjoyed treating me like trash
It was the one thing that made them feel better about their own pathetic lives
I'm happy they're dead
They deserved what happened to them
Dasu
I'm sorry, I just...
The details of the situation may vary from person to person
But everyone in our group has had a similar experience
All of you feel like that?
Yes
I'm able to create medicines and potions that are far more effective than the magic of an average recovery mage
So my skills are quite valuable
Despite that, I was still shunned for my lack of mana
Occasionally, people would rely on my expertise
But once my usefulness had run its course, they wanted nothing more to do with me
That's what happened to me too
I spent countless nights poring over my books while my peers were out having fun
I always had to work so hard
So did I
Me too
We all did
Everyone made fun of us because we couldn't use magic
Sometimes it felt like we didn't even exist
But that's over now
We're leaving this awful place
Look at these poor souls
We met them on our way to the Spade Kingdom and realized they had suffered the same terrible things
But they lived in the shadows
So we never would have known about them
I had no idea this many residents of the Clover Kingdom were dealing with such discontent
To think that all these people understood our pain and wanted to help us
And you
How dare you tell us to go back now?
You would have us return to that miserable existence?
We've had enough
You of all people should understand
Trust me, I get it
Asta
I know how much it sucks
That's exactly why I have to stop you
What is it about the Spade Kingdom that makes you so desperate to fight alongside them?
We want to gain the Devil's power
You're kidding!
Cobway from the Magic Parliament told us there was a Devil in the Spade Kingdom
We thought if we went there
The strength of that great being might be shared with us
I crave power
All of our people do
After aligning with the Spade Kingdom and receiving the Devil's overwhelming might
We'll return to Clover
And seek revenge
Come on
Don't do this
The three Leaves of a Clover are said to contain integrity, hope, and love
The fourth Leaf is given over to good luck
And in the fifth Leaf dwells a Devil
Isn't that how the saying goes?
That's right
Even though you had no mana and couldn't use magic
You still gained the Devil's blessing because you had this grimoire
You joined the Magic Knights and accomplished great things
You have no idea how much we admire you
Don't admire me
Not for that
We want to become like you
That's why we're going to Spade
Once we have the Devil's power, we can be reborn
And then our suffering will be avenged
That is our only objective
But I'm different
Different?
That's right
I trained my butt off to make up for not having any magic
And people still treated me like crap
I've spent my whole life being made fun of too
But I never hated anybody for it
It's true
I was able to use the Devil's anti-magic because I had that grimoire
But I never once thought about using it to get revenge on the Clover Kingdom
Or to punish any of the people who treated me badly
I only used it to help
Whether they're rich or poor
Royalty or commoner
I just want everybody to be happy
I can only imagine how happy we could have been if we looked at the world the way you do
Indeed
However, the flames of our hatred cannot be quenched
Which is why we won't be releasing your friend
We'll continue our journey towards Spade
Sure, whatever
But Nero's staying right here
Did you not hear me?
Then let me go instead
Oh no
Wouldn't it be better to have me too, not just my grimoire?
You went after both of us the first time you showed up
So obviously I was part of your plan
Fine, but we'll have to restrain you
Of course
And her too
What?
Now let Nero go like you promised
We'll be glad to do that
After we safely deliver you to the Spade Kingdom
You just made a mistake
Nah, don't worry
I have faith in them
We'll do whatever it takes to win the Devil's favor
And the more gifts we can offer
The better our chances
Asta and his grimoire
The girl who used forbidden magic
And a royal as well
I think they'll be pleased with this
That's if we get through the strong magic region
Yes, of course
Now let's proceed
We're at the border
Almost there
Get ready
I can feel it
Full moon or not
The mana's so strong
It's overwhelming
How do you plan to do this?
As you know
Our magic capability
Is basically non-existent
But not entirely
We do possess a small amount of mana
Using my catalyst magic
I can gather the scraps of mana
We each possess
And combine them into something great
Just as even the tiniest drops of water
Can become an unstoppable current
Dasu's catalyst magic
Will draw all of our strength together
And then we can use that power
To survive the strong magic region
That's crazy
Maybe
But it's our best shot
There's too much distance to cover
And no way to be sure
That your mana will hold out
Until we get there
This won't work
I understand it's a gamble
But at least one of us might make it
And perhaps that person
Will obtain the devil's power
There's no turning back
We must see this plan through to the end
Or we won't get revenge
On the Clover Kingdom
You can't
Let's proceed
Yes
What's that?
Sorry to keep you waiting
The cavalry's here
Magna
Captain Yami
I don't know.